Love Locks is a tv movie, romance, drama film directed by Martin Wood.
Lindsey Wilson first found love in the romantic city of Paris when
she was a university student studying art there.
Now, twenty years later, she is returning to the City of Light
to take her daughter on an adventure there.
With a little inspiration from the city's famed "love locks" on its scenic bridges, the adventure proves to be a journey of romance and rediscovery for the
divorced Lindsey when she reconnects with her college flame in Paris and finds that her first love just might be the lasting love of her life after all.
Lindsey Wilson, played by Rebecca Romijn.
Jack Burrow, played by Jerry O'Connell.
Hugo Blanchet, played by Bruce Davison.
Trent Greer, played by David Julian Hirsh.
Alexa, played by Jocelyn Hudon.
Jean-Paul, played by Benjamin Sutherland.
A love lock or  love padlock is a padlock that couples lock to a bridge, fence,
gate, monument, or similar public fixture to symbolize their love.
Typically the sweethearts' names or initials, and perhaps the date, are inscribed on the padlock,
and its key is thrown away (often into a nearby river) to symbolize unbreakable love.
Since the 2000s, love locks have proliferated at an
increasing number of locations worldwide.
They are treated by some municipal authorities as litter or
vandalism, and there is some cost to their removal.
However, there are other authorities who embrace them, and who use
them as fundraising projects or tourist attractions.
The tone is emotional.